as we go to our next game Siri MD Siri
MD a recent study showed that AI
assistants like Siri and Microsoft
Cortana really suck when it comes to
answering serious medical questions uh
although should probably be no surprise
that you shouldn't trust your health to
the same program you used to find nearby
mozzarella sticks and Anime porn so
comedians what are some other questions
you should not trust to the little
person inside your phone in 60 seconds
and begin Ria Siri why does Neil grass
Tyson want to take the joy out of
everything Damon Siri what's the best
way to sink my wife's period to my
[Laughter]
period AR you just supposed to like blow
your own hormones into her face or
something like no no Chris not into her
[Laughter]
face Jenny Siri how do I get one
direction to give me a hand job all
right points Cameron Siri what should I
do with this OJ knife
points Siri where is the closest diner
drivein or
dive Jenny Siri do you think Marco Rubio
stopped crying yet
F Siri where in the world is kman San
Diego all right
point